<?xml version="1.0"?>
<xml>
    <!---Titles need to be displayed inside <h3> HTML sections, while text in <p> sections---->
    <article>
        <title>IBM Lotus iNotes updates</title>
        <type>icon fa-flag-o</type>
        <text>Normally the emails on iNotes are ordered by date, from the most recent one to the last recent one. Thi way, when a new email is received, it is signaled as a number close to the link "Inbox" (e.g. Inbox(2)). Nevertheless, iNotes does not update the emails displayed in the inbox folder. <br/>
        To solve this problem we need to keep only the latest emails in the inbox folder while putting all the past emails in either the bin or some folder, like an “archive” folder. Then, we need to set up our preferences so that the emails are displayed in the reverse order, with the latest emails displayed last, at the bottom. It looks better and allows the service to actually show the new emails when they arrive.</text>
    </article>
    <article>
        <title>[HTML, CSS, JS] Hiding text after 100 words.</title>
        <type>icon fa-code</type>
        <text>Having a website were many articles are shown at the same time I had to find out a way to put an upper bound to the number of words that can be shown in the main page, allowing the user to read the full article through a link only if interested.<br/>
		For this purpose I realized a <a href="assets/js/articlesPreview.js" title="left click download the library">JS library</a> that includes the function normalizeMyArticles( xmlSourceFile, numWords, sectionID ).<br/>
		Once inculded the file in the webpage one can invoke it passing the name of the XML file containing the articles, the maximum number of words to display for each article and the CSS ID name that will be applied to the HTML sections while adding the text to the webpage.</text>
    </article>
    <article>
        <title>Stiff laptop hinge</title>
        <type>icon fa-laptop</type>
        <text>It is not a surprise for laptops to have problems from time to time, but the one I found to be a fine piece of hell is a tight hinge. At the beginning you think that the computer will hold and you only need to apply more strength while opening the lid, but when you not only find difficulties opening your laptop but start to hear some cracking noises from it while moving the lid then you realize your computer is not made of titanium. The problem is that even if the outer part may be in alluminium the small pieces that hold the screws that keep the hinge in place is made in simple, plain, plastic. This means that ...
		if your hinge is too tight and you don't pay attention to it at one point the plastic supports will brake and you may find yourself in trouble.</p>
		<p>In order to avoid such consequences I would advise you to send it to the lab to fix it ASAP. Otherwise you may find yourself in my same situation, having to completely open your laptop just to expose that hinge. Then you'll be able to unscrew it a little using a parrot-head plier or similar tool to hold one part of the screw and move the nut with another plier. It is a difficult operation, because, first, it is not easy to unscrew a tight hinge and, second, you do not have much space around it so you may end up breaking some other part while working on the hinge.</p>
		<p><strong>Summary</strong>: if you feel like the hinges of the computer are too tight do not assume the laptop will last forever anyway. Fix it before it's too late or ask somebody else to fix it for you.</text>
    </article>
    <article>
        <title>The Bloc Num button is set as OFF in Linux Netrunner 17</title>
        <type>icon fa-laptop</type>
        <text>If you are used having the Bloc Num button ON in your PC and you decide to try the Linux version "Netrunner 17" you may find yourself having the Bloc Num button always set as OFF.</p>
		<p>In order to avoid having to push the button every time you turn on your PC you can go to: System Settings -> Input devices -> Hardware.</p>
		<p>In the latter section you will find the option to set the Bloc Num as ON during the start-up of the KDE environment.</text>
    </article>
    <!---
    <article>
        <title>This is a title</title>
        <type>icon fa-laptop</type>
        <text>This is an example of content.</text>
    </article>
    --->
</xml>
